Divac online
Oh Youth truly is wasted on the young
[Music]
I bet you got up to all sorts of trouble
when you were my age
it's Mickey someone must be hacking I
hope we don't get banned for this
jenji I heard you used to have all the
high scores here that's right
weight used to hey where did they all go
diva in the flesh Oh can I get your
autograph only if I could get yours too
I love your new album
lucio how's my favorite international DJ
I play a lot of music but you're still
my favorite song
you know I've always wanted to know does
that thing have a stereo stereo you
gotta have true 3d sound to be
competitive duh
Divac just tell me one thing where'd you
learn to shoot like that 16-bit hero
me I love reading your journal I'm so
jealous you get to go to all those
places that's true I guess you don't get
to travel very much
hey was wondering if you'd sign
something for me it's again for a friend
of course here you go love
Deva hey was wondering if you'd sign
something for me it's again for a friend
Oh after this match is over right now
it's time to get serious
the destruction caused by the omnec
spear it reminds me of home things can
be destroyed but as long as the people
are strong they can always be rebuilt
isn't a game are you sure life isn't a
game
soldier 76
I can't stand you hackers you get those
of us with skill a bad name
you know that isn't the kind of hacking
I do right
hey Sombra i hear you're a master of
unlocking what are you talking about
any chance you'd let me peek under the
hood of your make whoever built your
mech did a good job
none that AI mess well if you want to
give me some upgrades I'm all ears
this is no place for children who are
you calling a child
this is no place for children hey I'm no
ankle biter
a giant gorilla just like in those old
video games I did that a lot
Divac have you seen the swatter course
now that is what I call a Mac size isn't
everything
[Music]
your SATs finished Lucio
Oh too slow chaser
to Russia With Love diva
I think your clocks off
it's a good thing I brought an umbrella
maybe next time
I think this pigs a little undercooked
no hats for you
oh by the way I know I say this a lot
please don't actually nerf this okay